adsonmedia.com 2017-08-24

# Adsonmedia

(applies to all visitors of Adsonmedia website, including our Publishers and Advertisers)

At Adsonmedia we are deeply committed to respect and protect the privacy of the visitors of Adsonmedia website (www.Adsonmedia.com) and our service users. Our privacy policy governs the way in which we use and disclose any personal information we may learn about you when you visit Adsonmedia website or use our services.

You must disclose clearly any data collection, sharing and usage that takes place on any site, app or other property as a consequence of your use of any Adsonmedia advertising service. By using Adsonmedia website, services, advertisement serving or any other related product you signify your acceptance of this policy.

## 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE

Adsonmedia adheres to the privacy guidelines created by the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) and Direct Marketing Association (DMA).

Adsonmedia collects information that you share to Adsonmedia yourself, e.g. when you complete Adsonmedia account registration form. This information may include, but is not limited to, your first and last name(s), company name and info (if any), email, address and phone number.

Adsonmedia uses the information that you have shared for providing you Adsonmedia services. Adsonmedia may also use this information for infoing you for marketing purposes and share it with third parties solely to perform services on behalf of Adsonmedia, such as providing support to Adsonmedia,s internal operations.

Adsonmedia may disclose any information we have about you (including your identity) if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of Adsonmedia website, or to identify, info or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Adsonmedia rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to or users of the Adsonmedia website, including Adsonmedia customers. Adsonmedia reserves the right at all times to disclose any information that Adsonmedia deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Adsonmedia also may disclose your information when Adsonmedia determines that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes.

You acknowledge and agree that Adsonmedia may preserve any transmittal or communication by you with Adsonmedia through the Adsonmedia website or any service offered on or through the Adsonmedia website, and may also disclose such data if required to do so by law or Adsonmedia determines that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal process, (2) enforce your Contract with Adsonmedia, (3) respond to claims that any such data violates the rights of others, or (4) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Adsonmedia, its employees, users of or visitors to the Adsonmedia website, and the public.

Adsonmedia, through IP tracking and the use of cookies and pixel tags, collects anonymous usage statistics. These are industry standard technologies used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. Information that is collected may include:

  * Session data
  * Geography
  * Browser information
  * IP Address
  * Operating system type

Adsonmedia may share the data which is collected using IP tracking, cookies and pixel tags to our customers only in the form of anonymous statistics so that it contains no personally identifiable information.

## 3\. COOKIE USAGE

Like most Internet sites, our Adsonmedia website may use cookies.

Cookies are small text files placed on the browser or hard drive of your computer, mobile, or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used when providing online services and help to make websites work, or work more efficiently as well as to provide information to the website owners. Cookies do lots of different things, for example, remembering user preferences, letting users navigate between pages efficiently and generally improving the user experience. Cookies are not used to personally identify you in any way, nor will they damage your system or files.

We may use on our Adsonmedia website the following cookies:

### Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies enable services that you have specifically requested for. Strictly necessary cookies are essential for the operation of Adsonmedia website. They let you move around Adsonmedia website and use its essential features, e.g. cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of Adsonmedia website or cookies used by our networking systems (such as load-balancers, or network protection tools). 

### Analytical / performance cookies

These cookies collect information about how you use Adsonmedia website. Such information is aggregated, anonymous and not personally identifiable and is used to help us improve how Adsonmedia website works and to understand what interests our users, e.g. these cookies can recognize and count Adsonmedia website visitor numbers and see how visitors move around Adsonmedia website. 

### Functionality cookies

These cookies allow Adsonmedia website to remember the choices that you make, (e.g. user name or language), and enable us to provide enhanced, more personal features, greet you by name and remember your preferences to improve your experience. They may be used to provide services that you have asked for. The information collected may be anonymized and these cookies cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. 

### Targeting or advertising cookies

These cookies collect information about how you use Adsonmedia website. Such information is aggregated, anonymous and not personally identifiable and is used to help us improve how Adsonmedia website works and to understand what interests our users, e.g. these cookies can recognize and count Adsonmedia website visitor numbers and see how visitors move around Adsonmedia website. 

### Session cookies

These cookies allow us to link your actions during a browser session. We use session cookies to support the functionality of Adsonmedia website and to understand your use thereof, i.e. which pages you visit, which links you use, and how long you stay on each page. Session cookies expire after you close your browser. 

### Persistent cookies

These cookies do not expire immediately after you close your browser, but stay on your device until they expire after a set period of time or you delete them. Each time you visit Adsonmedia website, our web server will recognize the persistent cookie on your computer's hard drive. By assigning your computer a persistent, unique identifier, we are able to create a database of your previous choices and preferences. The unique identifier also helps us to keep a more accurate account of how often you visit Adsonmedia website, how often you return, how your use of Adsonmedia website may vary over time, and the effectiveness of our promotional efforts. 

You can find more information about the cookies we use and the purposes we use them for in the tables below. By using Adsonmedia website, you agree we can place these cookies on your device:

First Party Cookies (i.e. cookies set on Adsonmedia website by us):

Cookie | Purpose | Duration type  
---|---|---  
Session tracking | These are first party cookies, which are both strictly necessary and functional. They gather information to maintain your login details throughout the session, avoiding re-authentication.  | Session cookies  
Site setting | They store temporary information to enable site functionality and collect and hold certain information which improves your experience on Adsonmedia website, e.g. by setting you the appropriate language. | Functionality cookies  
Behavior Tracking | These cookies are first party analytical/performance cookies. They are behavior tracking and error management cookies, which provide information regarding your visits to Adsonmedia website and the pages you visit. This information enables us to improve Adsonmedia website and monitor errors in respect thereof. The information collected by these cookies does not include any personally identifiable information and none of the information collected is passed to any third parties. | Persistent cookies  
Visit Analytics | They are used to identify whether you visit Adsonmedia website for the first time or you have visited it before. The information collected by these cookies does not include any personally identifiable information and none of the information collected is passed to any third parties. | Persistent cookies  
  
Third Party Cookies (i.e. cookies set on Adsonmedia website by third parties):

Cookie | Purpose | Duration type  
---|---|---  
Google Analytics | These are third party analytical cookies which are used by Google to help us learn about the traffic to Adsonmedia website. They are used to collect information about how visitors use Adsonmedia website, including details in respect of the number of visitors to the Adsonmedia website, where visitors have come to the Adsonmedia website from and the pages they visited. We use the information to compile reports about how visitors use Adsonmedia website and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, (none of these cookies collect and/or store any personally identifiable information). In addition to ourselves, Google accesses the information collected by these cookies. Further details in respect of these cookies and what they are used for can be found by found by following this link to the [Google website](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/gajs/cookie-usage). | Persistent cookies  
Google Doubleclick Remarketing Cookies | These cookies are third party advertising cookies, which are deployed on users' devices by Google. DoubleClick uses cookies to improve advertising. Some common applications are to target advertising based on what's relevant to a user, to improve reporting on campaign performance, and to avoid showing ads the user has already seen. DoubleClick cookies contain no personally identifiable information. Sometimes the cookie contains an additional identifier that is similar in appearance to the cookie ID. This identifier is used to identify an ad campaign to which a user was exposed previously; but no other data is stored by DoubleClick in the cookie, and none of the data is personally identifiable. The information collected and/or stored by these cookies is only made available to ourselves and Google and not to any other third parties. | Targeting and advertising cookies  
  
Please note that third parties, (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services), may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

Cookies can also be used for Pixel tracking which is explained below.

Adsonmedia Publishers and Advertisers have to ensure that the privacy policies of their Sites include correct information about cookie usage for advertisement purposes. As Adsonmedia may use third-party cookies on Publisher sites displaying Adsonmedia ads, Adsonmedia Publishers must have and abide by a privacy policy that discloses that third parties (i.e. Adsonmedia) may be placing and reading cookies on their users' browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of advertisement serving on the Publisher site.

It is possible to tell your browser to reject cookies for all sites or specific sites. Rejecting cookies is not recommended, however, as cookies are intended to improve your browsing experience. For more information about removing cookies, please see the "Opting Out" section below.

## 4\. Pixel tracking

To ensure the correct delivery and effectiveness of our Advertisers' advertising campaigns, our Advertisers undertake to place on their Sites pixel-tracking tags to measure usage statistics. 

Adsonmedia Advertisers can place pixel tags also on their partners' websites (i.e. websites belonging not to Advertisers but third parties to where Traffic is directed through the Advertiser's ads). These tags allow our software to measure non-personal behavioral patterns to indicate the effectiveness of the advertising. No personally identifiable information is collected during this process. 

## 5\. Audience pixels

In order to ensure that Internet users are getting the best level of advertising, our Advertisers undertake to place also audience pixels to track the activity of Internet users and match ads to users. Audience pixels do not store any personally identifiable information. 

We use audience pixels to match advertisements that may be of interest to Internet users or to assist our Advertisers and Publishers to deliver advertisements and offers that may be of interest to users within a given segment. 

The activity information collected during this process is not used in any other way by Adsonmedia or its clients other than to serve advertisements. 

## 6\. Opting out

To avoid storing information in your browser, you can easily deny, or opt out of, cookies either by:

(a) Manually deleting them (follow the instructions contained in the "Help" section of your browser).

(b) Choosing to permanently opt-out from seeing advertisements matching your interests.

In order to opt-out, you must have cookies enabled. If you use a different computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to repeat the process. If you wish to see ads tailored for you, please opt-in again. 

## 7\. Your rights

If you do not wish to receive any more commercial notifications from Adsonmedia, you may opt-out of this by sending an email request to info@Adsonmedia.com. In your email, please indicate which mode(s) of communication you would like to opt-out of (postal mail, email or telephone info). 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you in accordance with data protection laws. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. 

In addition you have all other rights provided in applicable laws regulating data protection and electronic transmission of commercial notifications. 

## 8\. Confidentiality and security

Adsonmedia adheres to the generally accepted industry standards to protect the information you submit to us. You agree and acknowledge that the Internet may be subject to breaches of security and that the submission of data over the Internet may not be secure. We strive to use acceptable means to protect any information you share with us, however we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
